(Grrah)
(Stop playing with 'em, RIOT)
Big guy, big guy, big-big guy, big guy
SpongeBob, big guy pants, okay (grrah)
Big guy, big guy, big-big guy, big guy (grrah)
SpongeBob, big guy pants, okay (like grrah)
SpongeBob, big guy pants, okay
Off the wake-up, I'm feelin' my best (like)
I bend over, I do my lil' stretch (like)
Ain't a jellyfish, but I'm the catch (like)
Feel like that fish, so I'm pumpin' my chest (grrah)
I blow bubbles so big like Mrs. Puff (grrah)
I be locked in, like no, this isn't luck (grrah)
Eatin' fancy, like no, this isn't chum (grrah)
With my bestie, like everything fun (grrah, grrah, grrah, grrah)
Big guy, big guy, big-big guy, big guy
SpongeBob, big guy pants, okay (grrah)
SpongeBob, big guy pants, okay (like)
SpongeBob, big guy pants, okay
Big things 'bout to happen today
I woke up feelin' a brand-new way
Facin' the world in a brand-new way
SpongeBob, big guy pants, okay
Tight fist, square hips
Doin' a dance in my big guy pants
The baddest, the top of the list, I am
And all my pearls, they came fresh out a clam
Big guy, big guy, big-big guy, big guy
SpongeBob, big guy pants, okay (grrah)
SpongeBob, big guy pants, okay (like grrah)
SpongeBob, big guy pants, okay
Off the wake-up, I'm feelin' my best
Big things 'bout to happen today (like)
I bend over, I do my lil' stretch
I woke up feelin' a brand-new way (like)
Ain't a jellyfish, but I'm the catch
Facin' the world in a brand-new way (like)
Feel like that fish, so I'm pumpin' my chest
SpongeBob, big guy pants, okay
Big guy, big guy, big-big guy, big guy
SpongeBob, big guy pants, okay (grrah)
SpongeBob, big guy pants, okay (like)
SpongeBob, big guy pants, okay